Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work!
Hello! Ste, this time with Danbaralulu from Juice-Juice and
Tea thing, and Momoko Kitahara.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much.
Now, Juice-Juice is going to be performing at the Halo!    On July 12, the same day that this Halo!
First of all, Pride of Light was written by Aoi Yamazaki.
The song is called "Pride of Light," so to put it simply, the main character is a girl whose pride shines through,
The song is about a girl whose pride shines through, so to put it simply, it is a song about a girl with a high pride,
The more you listen to the song, the more you will be able to interpret it in various ways, so I hope you will pay attention to the lyrics as well.
Funky Flashy is a cover of Tatsuro Yamashita's song.
This song is really bright and summery.
The music video was also very summery, shot by the pool, outside in the beautiful sunshine, and so on,
I think you can enjoy Juice-Juice in full bloom in summer.
Please enjoy both songs.
Ocha no Ame will also release their 3rd single on July 26th.
This time there are 4 songs in Quatroamento.
These four songs all have different atmospheres,
The song "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer" was written by Ms. Kami Hirose,
It is a very summery, bouncy and refreshing song.
The second song is called "Ochanoma, the place of doomed love, the place of Showa and Reiron, the place of love, the place of Showa and Reiron, the place of love, the place of Showa and Reiron, the place of love,
I don't care how long the title is,
This song is very cool and interesting at the same time,
This song is very cool and funny, and it is about Showa and Reiroon.
The third song is "Shekenare.
It is also the ending theme for TV Tokyo's Shadowverse Frame,
It has many lyrics that give me courage,
I hope everyone will listen to it and love it.
Finally, the fourth song is "Yoridorimidori.
This is a song that we usually perform a lot,
It is a very cute song with a lot of fruit names.
It's very cute.
Thank you very much.
Once again, Juice-Juice has released today.
And please do enjoy the single by Ocha no Onna as well.
Now, please take a look at this video first.
Please enjoy!
Invite someone to listen to it.
Let's spend the night that is about to begin.Let's spend the night that starts
Alone in my room, I'm never gonna be alone
♪ Clap your hands to the rhythm
♪ You're clapping your hands and humming her love song
♪ Step on the steps and you'll be dancing
Oh, let's play wonderful music
Let's dance till the wee hours of the morning
Let's make Funky night
Once you've heard it, you'll forget how lonely you are
Invite somebody to come and smell the kumquats
Let's spend the night that's about to begin
I can feel the heat coming from my heart
I can feel the heat in my heart I can feel the heat in my heart I can feel the heat in my heart
♪ You'll be humming her love songs ♪
Step on it. You're gonna hit it.
Wonderful music
Let's Dance By morning
Let's Make Party Night
Once you hear it, you'll be hooked You'll love it
Let's Dance By morning
I can feel the heat pouring out of your heart
I'm clapping my hands to the rhythm
I'll make your mouth sing so sweetly
I'm sure I can dance on the steps
Lovely Music Let's Dance
Pistol Let's Make till morning
Funky Night Oh Let's Play
Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning
Let's make funky night
Oh Let's play Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning
Let's make funky night
Oh Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning
Let's make funky night
Oh Let's
Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning
Let's make funky night
Oh Let's play Lovely MusicOh Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning
Let's make funky night
Thanks for watching!
Mizuki Danbara of Juice-Juice and Momo Kitahara of Ochanoma present "Halo! stay!
From here I would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I will ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them in a quick tempo.
Yes, I will do my best.
Momo Kitahara says she prefers gummy bears to rice sandwiches.
Yes, gummy bears that are a little crunchy.
What do you personally want people to hear about your third single, which will be released on July 26?
My thoughts on the end of the second song, "Ocha no Ma Hahoroba," "Ikoi no Ba," and "Shio mo Reimo Wacha Wacha Wacha.
Tomorrow, July 13th, marks the first anniversary of your major label debut.
My makeup has improved.
What do you pay most attention to when you sing?
The power of expression.
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. What was the first Hello! Project song you encountered?
What was the first song by Kobushi Factory's Dosokoi! KENKYO ni DADAIDAN by KOBUSHI FACTORY.
Thank you very much.
I was really interested in the first question about liking gummy bears,
Yes, that's right. I love gummy bears so much,
I am an honorary member of the Japan Gummy Association.
I am an honorary member of the Japan Gummi Association, and my activities consist of simply eating gummy bears,
I really love gummy bears.
What do you recommend?
I like the ones that are a little crunchy,
I eat them every day.
I love them.
One more question,
I wanted to ask you a personal question,
What do you pay most attention to when you sing? I thought you were very expressive,
I think you are very expressive,
So when you said "expressiveness," I thought, "Yes, that's right.
Expression has been important to me ever since I joined Ochanomizu,
But I have a habit of thinking about expressiveness first,
I had been thinking of valuing expressiveness first,
But recently, I have been thinking that I should put more importance on expressiveness first, and I have been able to build on that from the basics,
I hope to build on that with my expressive ability,
I am practicing hard on that.
I am looking forward to seeing more of you in the future.
I will do my best.I'll do my best.
Questions for Mr. Dambala after the VTR!
Hallo! STE!!!
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't.
I'll never kiss you okay.
Even you couldn't take it away
Pride Bright Now Scion
Oh Let's Play Lovely Music
Let's Dance Discoloring till Morning
Funky Flossing Now Scion
Is it the summer, or is it a dream?
Slightly Emotionally Unstable
Chachanoma New Single
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer, on sale July 26
Shake it up Power to believe in myself
Ordinary but forbidden
Chachanoma New Single
Chekenare January 26
Yoridori midori midori, I can't choose one I can't choose one
All the tokimei jan! Panpakapan all over the world
Before that, drink, drink, drink, drink
Yoridorimidori July 26th release
Hallo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Mr. Dambala.
Please do.
You have been a member of Juice-Juice for 7 years now.
What is your goal for this year?
To sing a lot.
It has been a little over a month since a new member, Mifusan Kawashima, joined the group.
What is your impression of Ms. Kawashima?
A bit of a crybaby.
What is the point of today's coordination?
It is a little simple, so I put on large earrings.
What is the latest dish you cooked?
Simmered bamboo shoots.
Dambara-san held a solo ballad-only event in April.
Which ballad from Hello! Project's past songs best suits you now?
The Vision" by Morning Musume。 16's "The Vision".
Thank you very much.
Now, I, Kitahara, would like to ask you about something that caught my attention,
First of all, I recently cooked a dish of bamboo shoots.First of all, the dish I recently cooked was bamboo shoots.
Yes! I happened to find some bamboo shoots called Madake at the supermarket,
You don't have to boil them, but you have to pre-boil them,
I happened to find bamboo shoots that can be used without boiling, so I bought them and made simmered dish.
How do you make simmered dishes?
You just need soy sauce, sake, sugar, and mirin (sweet cooking rice wine) to make it taste good,
That's how I made bamboo shoots.
Another key point of today's outfit is the large earrings,
They are so cute.
You're wearing cute ones too,
I like large earrings, and I like earrings that sparkle,
Today I wore asymmetrical earrings.
They are lovely.
Thank you.
Hallo! Sta. will continue after this.
This is Masashi Natsuyaki.
This is Honoka Kobayashi from Fions.
I will do my best again this time.
Now then, teacher, what would you like to make this time?
Today I would like to make a carrot cake.
Yay!
Carrot cake.
I love carrot cake.
I'm really looking forward to making it.
Be careful with this one, please. If you do it, you won't be able to play the piano.
That's right.
If you like cinnamon, put a bachikon in it.
Sure thing. Batikon.
So, where do we start this time?
Yes, I'm going to start with the paper cups. Now we are going to start baking, but in paper cups.
Yes.
It looks like a carrot.
Yes, it does.
It's 50,000 years old now.
It looks like a carrot.
Oh, it looks like a carrot. That's true.
That's true. I know there are sweets like this, right? Because they are.
Yes, there are.
Like sweets.
Yes, yes. It's shaped like rice.
The rice is half.The rice is half.
Yes, half. Half.
Even if it's shaped a little weird, it fits in.
Blend in?
Yes.
Now 170 degrees for about 20 minutes.
Yes, sir.
But it's small, so it might take 10 minutes.
Okay.
While the dough is baking, we'll make the frosting. Do you know frosting, Kobayashi?
Frosting? What do you think it is? We don't use it often.
I don't know.
Frosting is like the sugar coating on doughnuts.
Like a thin layer.
It's similar to that. It's powdered sugar dissolved in water.
That's called icing.
If you put cheese or butter or something in it, it's like frosting.
I learned that.
They put it in with the vatticon.
Butter and cream cheese, you put them out first, at room temperature.
If you're about to make it, you can use a microwave oven, even if you use 600W or a normal microwave oven, it will melt.
It will melt.
I left the cream cheese out for a long time.
It should be smooth.
Here's Miyahaze's point.
The cream cheese should be smooth.
Smooth it out.
Then smooth it out.
Smooth.
Like whipped cream.
It's very nice.
Butter and sugar.
There's a little bit of a gritty texture.
Flatten it with a spatula. - Flatten it with a spatula. - Flatten it with a spatula.
Smash them together.
Put the butter in.
50 grams of butter.
We want to make it smooth and pomaded.
I'd like to make it into a pomade.
I put it in.I put it in.
Pomaded
Pomade?
Pomade
What's a pomade castle?
What do you think it is?
You don't know what pomade is, do you?
I don't think so.
I don't hear much about it.
It's used by a lot of men to stiffen their hair.
Like this.
It's also used in pastries. Pomade castles.
Especially with butter.
I'm told to use pomade castles.
Haste?
Haste, you mean.
It's pomade.
It's called Pomade Castle.
I see.
I don't know.
This is Pomade Castle.
This is Pomade, too.
Pomade.
Mix them together.
If it's like this, it's perfect.
If you don't let it come to room temperature
If you don't let it come out at room temperature
If you don't let it come out at room temperature, it'll be mushy or something.
Smoothness is the key.
That's enough.
Then add vanilla extract.
That's right.
So much oil.
So much oil in the pomade.
You know what I'm saying?
It's got to have a little acidity to make it crispy.
Be careful not to get any seeds in it.
Yes, I've already put them in. The lemon will separate from the pomade.
It's too mushy in the pomade.
It's going to be crunchy.It's gonna be a little messy.
Safe, safe.
Yes, OK.
It's like this.
I thought it would go bad during baking.
If you put it in the fridge, it's not good.
It will get hard again, which is not a good thing at all.
It's really important to keep it at room temperature.
It's really room temperature.
Room temperature, room temperature.
It's room temperature.
I like the sound when I open it.
Smells good, though
Check.
Here you go.
It's almost there, if you can get it in there.
It's good.
It's a little sticky.
I think it's okay.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Yes, it's okay.
It's open.
Yes, it's open.
Let this cool down a little first.
Okay.
Don't touch it at all.
It's still warm.
I dyed it a lot.
And then...
This one here.
Frosting.
Frosting
Yes, sir.
While it's in this smooth state.
Put it on here.
Put it on.
Yes, sir.
And when this pomade becomes hard, it's done.And when this pomade-like substance hardens, it's done.
I see.
I don't have time today.
I forced it a little bit in the freezer.
in the freezer
I'm in a hurry.
I'd like to chill it hard.
Normally, I put it in the refrigerator for about an hour.
I'll let it cool in the refrigerator for about an hour.
Okay.
That's fine.
Leave it like that.
It's fine.
If you need more, just add more.
Okay, that's good.
That's good.
Good. - Good.
It's perfect.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's cooled down.
Okay, then.
I think I'm just going to do this one.
There's a seam here.
I'll flip it over.
Yes, indeed.
Oh!
This is really nice.
That's great.
Put it on.
Wow! That's so good! That's great!
Boom! I think it's better to cut a little bit than to cut a lot.
Chop it up!
A little bit of it.
Hoi!
Yes, OK!
So, it's done!
Yay!
The carrot cake is done!
What do you think, Kobayashi?
It's really cute, and since I made it myself, I'm very attached to it.Well, it's really cute already, and I love it because I made it myself.
That's for sure.
And it solidified properly,
It turned out to be a nice shape.
It turned out to be a cute shape.
Yes, it did. Then, please try it right away.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
It looks like there are a lot of ingredients in it.
Yes, it is. Plenty this time.
There are carrots and raisins in it.
It looks like there is a little bit of refined silver left in the carrots.
Yes, I'll have some.
Wow, there are so many flavors,
It's like a party.
Various flavors?
Wow, because each ingredient goes so well with each other,
This pommage on top.
Pomade.
It's all mixed together.
The pomade tastes like lemon and cheese,
I think the pomade tastes like lemon and cheese,
But the bottom one tastes like carrots,
I can taste the carrots.
Do I taste carrots?
It tastes like carrots and old meat,
There's a lot of different kinds of carrots in this one,
It's really tasty.
How was your experience in Hello Kitchen?
I've been watching Hello Kitchen videos for a long time,
I've been watching Hello Kitchen videos for a long time, and I've always wanted to do it someday,
I'm really happy to be here,
I'm also really happy to be here, and to be able to make carrot cake, which I'm really into right now,
I decided to make it at home for sure,
I decided to make it at home for sure.
So thank you again.
Thank you again.
That's all for Hello Kitchen.
It looked delicious.
Momo, do you cook these days?
Yes, I do. I, Kitahara, have not been cooking for a long time,Yes, that's right. I, Kitahara, have actually never cooked for a long time,
I finally started trying my hand at cooking when I was in my second year of high school,
These days I cook quite a bit.
What is the latest dish you have made?
I recently made a dish called crispy bell peppers,
The way to cook them is not just to cool them in ice water,
I only cool them in ice water to make them crispy,
They are quite tasty.
I think it is easy for everyone to imitate.
I have one question. Do you have a favorite dish?
I don't have a dish that I am good at,
I like simmered dishes a lot, so I make them,
I also like potatoes, so I often make potato salad, meat and potatoes.
I also dream of making meat and potatoes,
Is that so?
Please let me know next time.
Thank you very much.
Hello! Ste.
Next up was the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project has many heartbreaking lyrics,
I would like to recommend the lyrics of "Pride Bright" from the latest single,
All of them are wonderful, but especially the last one,
I especially like the last line, "Pride that won't be carried away by 'I love you'",
She is a girl who is proud throughout the whole song,
I thought the phrase "I love you, but I won't be carried away" was really cool,
It's a song about a girl whose pride shines through,
It's a song about a girl whose pride shines through, so I hope you will enjoy the lyrics as a whole. Momo-chan?
Yes, I am. I, Momo Kitahara, am from the latest single by Ocha-no-Ma,
The slightly emotionally unstable horn A-melody,
I, Kitahara, am singing,
There is a lyric that says, "Even the fashionable Tsunoi is unique,
I think it is my favorite lyric,
I am often told that I am unique,
I often wear purple all over my body,
I wear purple all over my body, even my shoes and backpack are purple,
I wear purple all over my body,
It's unique.
It's just like the lyrics,
The director chose the lyrics that are just like the lyrics of the song,
I hope you will pay attention to the lyrics.I hope you will pay attention to it.
Now, please watch the VTR.
Here it is!
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!    In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about their charms. Project's songs and talk about their charms. This week, I, Ruri Hiromoto, will be presenting.
Here it is. This is a song from Morning Musume。 I'm just saying that I have a lot of things to say, but I want to shine,
I wonder if I can become a real person,
The song is even more poignant when you hear it from the chorus phrase before the first verse,
The chorus of the song, "I wonder if I can become a real person," is even more poignant when you hear it from the chorus phrase that precedes the first verse,
But in this part of the song, you can't be so confident in yourself, can you? However, anyone who wants to have self-confidence in themselves can do so.
But everyone has that feeling of wanting to be confident.
So I wondered if I could become a real person.
I wonder if I can become the real thing.
I think it's really great that the desire to shine is so fully expressed.
That's great.
I think it's up to you to decide whether you are the real thing or not.
That's why I want to shine, and I want to go higher,
I can read the feeling of aiming for the top just from this phrase,
I thought it was really nice.
I also love "fake love," and I listen to it often,
I often listen to this song, and I thought it was a love lyric throughout the song,
I just want to shine like this,
I thought it was a really good song that gave me confidence in myself, not just in love.
It's a really good song that makes you want to do your best, so please give it a listen.
Please listen to it and enjoy the next episode!
Hello! STE!
With Bambalalulu of Juice-Juice,
Juice-Juice's Bambaralulu and Momoko Kitahara of Ochanoma will be presenting the next installment of "Halo! STE!
As I mentioned in the opening, Juice-Juice is releasing a new single today, July 12, and Ochanoma is releasing a new single on July 26,
Ochanoma will release a new single on July 26th.
Here I would like to introduce some points that I would like you to see in the music videos of the songs included in the album.
Yes, yes, yes. Seen, jan!
I'm Hanky Flassin's
"I'll be captivated!" in the lyrics of the song.
Akari Endo's "A fleeting wink!" I'm not talking about the lip scene, but the dance scene.
It's not a lip scene, but a close-up of the dance scene,
She is not looking at the camera or anything,
I was really moved by the use of this momentary miracle.
I hope you will see it.I am very impressed and I would like you to see that.
I hope you will see it. I, Kitahara, am a little bit unstable in the summer.
This is a poolside scene of Kitahara, Nishizaki and Kubota,
At first glance, it appears to be a scene of Kitahara, Nishizaki, and Kubota having fun by the pool,
At first glance, it appears to be a scene of Kitahara, Nishizaki, and Kubota by the pool, but it is actually a scene of them eating ice cream,
But actually, we were filming an ice cream eating scene right before that, and a dragon fly took the ice cream away from me.
It was my first experience,
It was my ice cream,
But right after that, there is a shot of the three of us playing with a beach ball,
So, I'm just telling you that such a thing happened.
The music videos are full of charms other than the ones mentioned here,
I hope you will enjoy all of the songs.
See you soon.
[ED
Human Hair Suckle Hair Three generations will never be like this.
Showing the same show on TV in the age of light, the show is mom.
Heart, bad hair, and spread out, all in different ways.
But it's so much better than the old days, when we had one show after another, and it was so annoying.
I want to be relieved, I want to be relieved, I want to be relieved. The human condition is still rooted in the same place.
I want to be relieved. I want to be relieved. I want to be relieved.
It's not just lip-synching. It's normal.
Mucha, Mucha, Mucha, Mucha, Mucha, No Love!
Zecche!
Online, offline, family, friends, passion.
Mucha! Mucha! Mucha! Mucha! Mucha!
Zecche! Zecche! Zecche! No Love!
One bite. Success. Love made in such a place.
You'll be born just the same
Swipe, step up your life
I'd rather see a passionate smile on someone's face than another world.
I want to be touched, I want to be excited, I want to be connected by something I love
Where heart to heart, heart to heart, hand to hand
I'm not just challenging you, I'm jumping in front of you
Step up, step up, step up, step up
Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha, cha-cha, cha-cha, audion
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha, magic parts
Music SNS Live or not Live or not
Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha Wocha
Well, well, well, well, well, a place for love
Comfy, comfy, comfy, comfy, comfy, comfy.
Only in such a moment can you dreamOnly in such a moment can you dream.
I'm sure you can't see it.
Wacha, tea room.
Tea room, tea room... I'm in love with you...
La La La La
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for everything. I'm rooting for you too.
This is Danbaralulu from JuiceJuice and Momo Kitahara from Ochanama.
Momo Kitahara of Ochanama presents Halo! Sta.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Today, July 12th, Juice-Juice's new single
Pride Bride Funky Flushy" has been released!
The song is full of Juice-Juice's strength and the song is a cover of Tatsuro Yamashita's "Pride Bride".
and a cover song by Tatsuro Yamashita.
Both songs are really beautiful, so please listen to them!
And Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour
Juice-Juice Encore will start on July 23rd!
A new member, Mifuyu Kawashima, will be joining us in Japan, so please look forward to it!
Please look forward to it!
Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary is still going to be a lot of fun!
And on August 4th, Juice-Juice will perform at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023!
Juice-Juice will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023 on August 4!
This will be our second year in a row, so we are really looking forward to it!
And on August 13th, Juice-Juice will be performing at Dokkin Japan Festival 2023.
Juice-Juice will perform for the first time in 4 years!
We are really looking forward to it, and we hope to have a lot of fun this summer.
We are really looking forward to it and hope to have a lot of fun this summer!
Please come and see us!
Thank you very much!
Yes, Ocha no Ma is going to release its 3rd single on July 26th!
A little unstable summer
Ocha no Ma, Mahoro Bai, Koi no Ma
Shio amore imo wacha wacha wacha
Shake na Are
We will be releasing more than a few singles!
Please love the various tea horses!
From August 5, Tea Horse Concert 2023
SUMMER! More Growing Up will start!SUMMER!More Growing Up is starting!
We will try our best to grow up more and more!
And Ochanomaha will perform at many events this summer!
Let's enjoy this summer with Tea Horse!
And on Sunday, November 19th
We will hold a concert on Sunday, November 19th in Bizen City, Kokura Prefecture!
This time, the ticket comes with a Bizen ware of Tea Horse.
The ticket comes with a Bizen City tax return gift!
For more information, please visit our website!
Hello! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Ruru Danbara from Juice-Juice and Momo Kitahara from Ocha no Ma.
Ruru Danbara from Juice-Juice and Momo Kitahara from Ochanoma.
Good bye!